[Once Annie dilutes your shares,]
[you'll have no leverage.]
[You won't even be able to]
[provide for Mumu.]
[To Annie,]
[he's just the child of you and Zhou Jiansheng.]
Mumu, don't you love fish the most?
Why haven't you touched it?
The cook didn't pay attention today
and left some big bones.
I'm worried he might choke,
so they switched to abalone porridge.
You'd better decide
if you want to stay as a golden canary in the shelter,
or teach this child to walk.
After all, when the Lu family has taken everything from you,
this child can still run on his own.
Sell all 4% of my shares in Golden Thread,
and transfer the funds to Union Bank of Switzerland.
If my mother
finds out about this,
you know
what will happen.
Mr. Zhuang
I have news on what you asked.
Acquire the four percent no matter what the cost.
Even using the Film Fund's reserves.
Yes.
Annie
If you know your daughter
is destroying herself now,
I believe
your expression now
must be very interesting.
15.9 yuan has been paid.
My sister already knows.
Your mission has failed.
I will give you some money
to leave Lucheng forever.
You just give up?
Young Master Lu is less courageous than I thought.
Isn't it more interesting now?
What do you want to do?
Once a crack appears,
it will only get deeper.
Lu Qianqian's resistance
proves that she is wavering.
Don't play word games.
What exactly do you want?
I want to cure your inner demons.
For example,
to help you get the person you've longed for.
[Before the release of Dark Fairy Tale,]
[it's your last chance.]
You're really here.
Lu Qianqian has sold 4% of the shares.
Faster than I expected.
Did you buy them?
She got there first.
Young Master Shen, you're actually half a step behind.
That's not like you.
What's this?
You're investigating me?
There shouldn't be any secrets between allies,
right?
You approached Lu Xu to enter the Lu family,
and everything you did was to avenge your sister.
Am I right?
Because Zhou Jian
was your brother-in-law,
and the one who took him away
was Lu Qianqian.
You really have a lot of connections.
That's right.
I'm Su Muchen's unknown sister,
Su Muli.
Our parents were
the owners of a small chemical fiber plant.
The factory is on fire!
But a fire
took away our loved ones.
Chen!
Take your sister.
And my childhood.
Mom is still in the warehouse.
I'll go get her out.
Leave now!
The warehouse is about to explode!
Dad!
[After that fire,]
[we were sent to an orphanage together.]
[My sister showed remarkable strength for her age.]
Don't be afraid.
From today on,
[this is your home.]
[She took care of me,]
[and supported me]
[with her young shoulders.]
[In the orphanage,]
[we depended on each other.]
[She always gave me the best,]
[telling me stories about our parents every night,]
[singing the lullabies my mother used to sing,]
[and keeping the memory of home]
[alive in my heart.]
I've shown you mine. You should show me yours.
Let's go.
Li,
our parents said
this tree is our family.
Yeah.
If we have something to tell them,
we can write it down and bury it here.
They will hear us.
Yeah.
By the way, Li,
what secret did you write today?
I'm not telling you.
That's my secret with the big tree.
[She is my only family,]
[and the only tie I have.]
[With her protection,]
[my childhood was at least not so broken.]
[Three years later,]
[a couple of overseas Chinese from abroad]
[adopted me from the orphanage.]
Xiao Li,
I made this myself.
No matter where you go,
I will always be your sister.
Yes.
When the locust trees bloom every year,
we'll meet here.
When you grow up, I'll go to find you.
We'll live together again.
Yes.
This is our promise.
[My adoptive parents adopted me]
[because I looked like their deceased daughter.]
[Jiang Li is also her name.]
[But I always opposed changing my name.]
[So later, all my documents were under the name Su Muli.]
[Only at home, they would call me Jiang Li.]
[Although we were separated by oceans,]
[our sisterly bond never broke.]
[Every summer,]
[I would return to the orphanage to reunite with my sister.]
[We would share our lives with each other.]
[These brief reunions]
[became the most precious moments for us.]
This way, the rain won't get in.
Sis,
I've talked to my adoptive parents.
Come to France with me.
Then we can see each other every day
instead of just once a year.
Li,
I can't leave yet.
This place still has the scent of Mom and Dad.
and memories of us.
And
I met someone very important.
Did you forget our promise?
You said
when you grew up,
you would come to me.
We would live together again.
Li,
he's Zhou Jian.
He's a very gentle person.
Xiao Li, be good.
When you grow up,
you will understand.
So I can't leave yet.
Liar!
Are you going to betray our promise for a man?
Xiao Li,
I hope you can understand me.
Since you chose someone else,
then let's pretend we never made any promises.
I couldn't understand her choice at that time.
Xiao Li.
I thought she gave up our kinship
for a man.
In the four years,
I never replied to any message she sent me.
When I was 19,
I received the news that she was pregnant.
Xiao Li.
I'm pregnant.
I'm going to tell Zhou Jian next month.
to give him a surprise.
Li,
I really miss you.
Dear.
Dear,
why are you crying so hard?
Aunt Lu,
I want to go back
to see my sister next month.
Okay.
Remember to bring more thick clothes.
Autumn in the hometown
is always cold suddenly.
Yes.
Pride finally gave way to longing.
I decided to go back to see her.
When the plane landed,
I was thinking about how to surprise her.
But I didn't expect
I was the one who was at a loss.
Three days ago, on a rainy night,
Muchen was drunk at the crossroad.
The driver of the speeding truck couldn't brake in time.
So,
the driver who hit your sister
also hit the roadside railing and died.
Today I met a silly boy named Zhou Jian.
I don't know if Li would like Zhou Jian.
We quarreled today.
Li will go back to France tomorrow.
We won't meet again until a year later.
Li is really something.
She hasn't replied to my messages for years.
We've graduated.
I believe that even though Zhou Jian and I have nothing now,
we will get better and better.
I miss Li so much.
I wonder how she's doing abroad.
I really want her to meet Zhou Jian.
If he doesn't propose to me,
I'll propose to him.
Come on, Su Muchen.
[We're going to have a baby.]
[There's lipstick on his collar.]
[Li Xiaorou said Lu Qianqian is pregnant.]
[Annie came to me]
[and asked me to divorce Zhou Jian.]
[What should I do?]
[I found my sister's diary under the old tree.]
[I learned that Zhou Jian cheated on Lu Qianqian.]
[After Lu Qianqian got pregnant,]
[Annie forced my sister to divorce Zhou Jian.]
[The moment I saw Zhou Jian with Lu Qianqian,]
[my heart was completely broken.]
[So I changed my name to Jiang Li.]
[At that time, I was too weak]
[to shake the Lu family, a deeply rooted tree.]
[But from that day on,]
[my old dreams were shattered.]
[I walked on a tempered road,]
[leaving a mark of revenge with every step.]
[I've finished my story.]
[Now,]
[are you still willing to cooperate?]
You don't have to turn yourself into a blade.
There are many ways to revenge.
Since I saw my sister's diary,
I had no choice.
Shen Jingmo,
you are crazy.
Leave Zhou Jian
and Lu Xu.
They don't deserve to make your hands dirty.
Let me help you.
If you want to learn from Zhuang Wan to do speculative business,
I welcome you.
But don't approach me under the name of redemption.
The road I take is only dark.
And your life should be under the spotlight.
Don't get into this mess.